identityrpg.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy Policy

Asylum Entertainment takes your privacy seriously.

Asylum Entertainment Inc. ("Asylum") is committed to protecting the privacy of any personal information that you may provide to us when using any of our online services.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Asylum may collect personally identifiable information if you purchase, download, or register any software products offered by Asylum or use any of our product websites. This information may include your name, address, email address, phone number, etc. This information is used only to record any sales transactions, to provide you with any product support, or to provide you with product information (such as updates, alerts and associated product offerings), via opt-in permission based email. If we use a payment processing and product fulfillment merchant we ensure that the same strict privacy criteria are in place. Asylum will never sell, rent, lease, or give your information to a third party unless required by law. If you have subscribed to receiving emails from Asylum or any Asylum affiliated company and you choose to no longer receive such emails, you may unsubscribe at any time by either clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in the email or by contacting Asylum directly. By transmitting any information to Asylum when prompted, you consent to Asylum’s collection and use of such information for the purposes as defined herein. You are responsible for making the decision on whether or not to proceed with any activity that requires your requests your personal information.

### COOKIES

Asylum's websites, such as this, may from time to time use cookies. A "cookie" is a unique text file that the Asylum Web site can send to your Internet browsing software in order to tailor information presented to you based on your browser settings and preferences. Cookies may also be stored on an Internet User’s computer for the purposes of tracking the Internet user’s clicks to ensure that they are directed to the correct click-through destination site, or to track the performance of its business partners and to ensure proper payment for their sales activities related to their business relationship with Asylum. Asylum’s usage of cookies does not collect any personal information in any way. If you do not want Asylum to deploy cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or notify you when a Web site tries to put a cookie in your browser software, however, rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use of some of the products and/or services at our website.

We use proprietary and third party cookies to improve your experience and our services. If you continue browsing, we shall consider that you accept their use.

### STATISTICAL INFORMATION

Asylum may track domain names, IP addresses, and browser types from Internet users who visit our Web site. We use this information to produce traffic statistics for the Asylum Web site, and to identify how we can improve our products, services, and Web site for our customers. Such information does not contain any personal information.

### THIRD PARTY LINKS

Asylum may from time to time include links from our website that may direct you to other third party websites which we believe may be of interest to you. Please take note that if you are directed to any third party websites, those websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy and it is your responsibility to review and understand the privacy policy of any websites that you visit.

### SECURITY

Any personally identifiable information that is collected by Asylum is stored in limited access servers. Asylum takes reasonable precautions and measures to protect the information that has been collected, and to safeguard the servers where such information is stored. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction.

### POLICY MODIFICATIONS

Asylum may from time to time make modifications to this Privacy Policy to ensure that we are in compliance with applicable regulations. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted promptly on this Privacy Policy web page and on the Home page.

### CONTACT

If you would like to contact us, or have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policies, please e-mail us at the following address:

Asylum Entertainment Inc.  
support@asylumentertainment.ca
